Guide to the Joseph Veverka papers, 1942-2013,
Veverka, Joseph papers,
- Series X. Audio/Visual Material
  - Deep Impact Critical Design Review, 2002-01-29-2002-01-31; CD-5055 (Box 14)
  - New Frontiers in the Solar System: An Integrated Exploration Strategy, Undated; CD-5056 (Box 14)
  - JPL Science Division Assessment, 2004-10; CD-5057 (Box 14)
  - Cassini at Jupiter' (w/sound), Undated; CD-5058 (Box 14)
  - ACM NExT, 2008-07; CD-5059 (Box 14)
  - Odysseus, 2009-07-27; CD-5060 (Box 14)
  - HiRISE 3-D APR09 28 Anaglyphs, Undated; CD-5061 (Box 14)
  - Stardust-NExT Side Visit, 2007-05-15; CD-5062 (Box 14)
  - COMPLEX Presentations, 2008-08-20-2008-08-22; CD-5063 (Box 14)
    committee on Planetary and Lunar Exploration-Space Studies Board-DEPS
  - JPL Visiting Committee on Earth Science, 2007-05-17-2007-05-18; CD-5064 (Box 14)
  - Canadian Space Agency Report 37th COSPAR Scientific Assembly, 2006-2007; CD-5065 (Box 14)
  - Joe Burns Symposium Poster Congrats Card, Undated; CD-5066 (Box 14)
  - Planetary Scientists A Pictoral Archive 1966-2006, 2006; CD-5067 (Box 14)
    Compiled by Dale Cruikshank and David Morrison
  - Sentimental Journey, Undated; CD-5068 (Box 14)
  - Assorted ASU Press Release Images, 2006-07-10; CD-5069 (Box 14)
  - Exploring the Solar System: Three Amazing Moons!, 2006-07-18; CD-5070 (Box 14)
    Cornell Adult Univ.
  - CCAT Posters New Poster 3, Undated; CD-5071 (Box 14)
  - ASTRO 490 Life on Mars, 2006-10-05; CD-5072 (Box 14)
  - Mars Presentation Steve Squyres, 2004-04-13; CD-5073 (Box 14)
  - Comets, 2011-01-04; CD-5074 (Box 14)
  - STERN-NExT Windows Autostart A., 2007-05-21; CD-5075 (Box 14)
  - STERN-NExT Windows Autostart B., 2007-05-21; CD-5076 (Box 14)
  - STERN-NExT Mac .PPT + .MOV, 2007-05-21; CD-5077 (Box 14)
  - Stardust-NExT 9P/Tempel 1 Flyby VCD for DVD player, Undated; CD-5078 (Box 14)
  - Stardust-NExT 9P/Tempel 1 Flyby VCD for DVD player No Menu, Undated; CD-5079 (Box 14)
  - ASTRO 202 Spring 2007 Lecture 2, 2007; CD-5080 (Box 14)
  - ASTRO 202 Spring 2007 Lecture 4, 2007; CD-5081 (Box 14)
  - ASTRO 202 Spring 2007 Lecture 5, 2007; CD-5082 (Box 14)
  - ASTRO 202 Spring 2007 Lecture 10, 2007; CD-5083 (Box 14)
  - ASTRO 202 Spring 2007 Lecture 11, 2007; CD-5084 (Box 14)
  - ASTRO 202 Spring 2007 Lecture 12, 2007; CD-5085 (Box 14)
  - ASTRO 202 Spring 2007 Lecture 13, 2007; CD-5086 (Box 14)
  - Veverka Birthday Symposiu, and events Cornell University, 2001-10-05-2001-10-07; CD-5087 (Box 14)
  - Astronomy Media Workbook Sixth Edition, 2009; CD-5088 (Box 14)
  - UMD, 2005-12-13-2005-12-14; CD-5089 (Box 14)
  - ASTRO 202 Spring 2007 Lecture 28, 2007; CD-5090 (Box 14)
  - CONTOUR Images KSC Media Services S/C Processing at KSC, 2002-04-25-2002-07-03; CD-5091 (Box 14)
  - ASTRO 202 Spring 2007 Lecture 19, 2007; CD-5092 (Box 14)
  - ASTRO 202 Spring 2007 Lecture 20, 2007; CD-5093 (Box 14)
  - ASTRO 202 Spring 2007 Lecture 23, 2007; CD-5094 (Box 14)
  - ASTRO 202 Spring 2007 Lecture 25, 2007; CD-5095 (Box 14)
  - ASTRO 202 Spring 2007 Lecture 27, 2007; CD-5096 (Box 14)
  - Viking Orbiter 1 Images of Mars Images 373A01 to 414A40, Undated; CD-5097 (Box 14)
  - Viking Orbiter 1 Images of Mars Images 416A01 to 443A10, Undated; CD-5098 (Box 14)
  - Voyagers to the Outer Planets Volume 17-Jupiter, 1994; CD-5099 (Box 14)
    Voyager ISS Images 16212.36 to 16340.10
  - Mision to Venus Magellan: Line of Sight Acceleration Profile Data, 1994-10; CD-5100 (Box 14)
  - Disk #14 of the Clementine raw data, 1994-12-16; CD-5101 (Box 14)
  - Voyager: SkyGazer College Edition Version 4.0, 2008; CD-5102 (Box 14)
  - Mission to Jupiter Calileo Images from Earth 2 Encounter, Undated; CD-5103 (Box 14)
    Raw Experiment Data Record Volume 11 - Images 165141200 to 165206645
  - Voyagers to the Outer Planets Volume 20 - Jupiter Voyager ISS Images 17373.10 to 19409.44, 1994-12; CD-5104 (Box 14)
  - CONTOUR, 2002-07-02; CD-5105 (Box 14)
  - Delta II CONTOUR Kennedy Space Center, Florida Cape Canaveral Air Force Station, Florida, 2002-04-25-2002-07-03; CD-5106 (Box 14)
  - Voyagers to the Outer Planets Volume 21 - Jupiter Voyager ISS Images 19409.47 to 19986.43, 1994-10; CD-5107 (Box 14)
  - Getting the Back off the Wlch T. Gold Buriel, 2009-11-11; CD-5108 (Box 14)
  - Mission to Jupiter Calileo Images from Earth 2 Encounter, Undated; CD-5109 (Box 14)
    Raw Experiment Data Record Volume 10 - Images 16033626 to 165141145
  - Mission to Jupiter Calileo Images from Earth 2 Encounter, Undated; CD-5110 (Box 14)
    Raw Experiment Data Record Volume 10 - Images 165033626 to 165141145
  - Stardust-NExT A Mission to Complete the Exploration of Comet Tempel 1 with Stardust, 2006-04-05; CD-5111 (Box 27)
  - Stardust-NExT Supplemental Disk Stardust-NExT Animation, 2007-03-20; CD-5112 (Box 27)
  - Comet Hopper Discovery 2010 Phase A Concept Study Report NNH10ZDA0070, 2012-03-19; CD-5113 (Box 27)
  - Stardust-NExT A Mission to Complete the Exploration of Comet Tempel 1 with Stardust, 2007-03-20; CD-5114 (Box 27)
  - Stardust-NExT Partial Proposal: Science Techncial Management EPO, 2007-03-20; CD-5115 (Box 27)
  - Stardust-NExT 9P/Tempel 1 Flyby PC/Win Autostart, Undated; CD-5116 (Box 14)
  - New Horizons Shedding Light on Frontier Worlds Ciritical Design Review, 2003-10-28-2003-10-31; CD-5117 (Box 27)
  - New Horizons Shedding Light on Frontier Worlds Ciritical Design Review, 2003-10-28-2003-10-31; CD-5118 (Box 27)
  - Stern - NExT .zip, 2007-05-21; CD-5119 (Box 14)
  - Stern - NExT PC/Windows Autostart, 2007-05-21; CD-5120 (Box 14)
  - Stardust NExT 9P/Tempel 1 flyby animations, Undated; CD-5121 (Box 14)
  - Startdust - NExT 9P/Tempel 1 Flyby VCD for DVD Player, Undated; CD-5122 (Box 14)
  - Eros in Color Web Stuff, Undated; CD-5123 (Box 14)
  - Extended Mission Proposal Messenger MErcury Surface, Space ENvironment, GEochemistry, and Ranging, 2011-02; CD-5124 (Box 14)
    Searn C. Solomon, PL
  - Mars Express 2006 "Face" Images, 2006; CD-5125 (Box 14)
  - Cisscal Release 1.1, 2000-12-18; CD-5126 (Box 14)
  - Next Steps in Deep Space, Undated; CD-5127 (Box 14)
    A cosmic Study by the International Academy of Astromautics
  - Tempel 1: Surface Processes and the Origin of Smooth Terrains, 2006-03; CD-5128 (Box 14)
  - CONTOUR slides: ambassador presentation, spacecraft construction, Undated; CD-5129 (Box 14)
  - Adobe Photoshop Elements 2.0, 1990; CD-5130 (Box 14)
  - ASTRO 202 Spring 2007 Lecture 15, 2007; CD-5131 (Box 14)
  - ASTRO 202 Spring 2007 Lecture 16, 2007; CD-5132 (Box 14)
  - Small Satellites Galileo, Undated; DVD-2936 (Box 14)
  - Cornell Caltech Atacam Telescope Cerro Chajnantor, Chile, Undated; DVD-2937 (Box 14)
  - CONTOUR Departs Earth, Undated; DVD-2938 (Box 14)
  - CONTOUR Launch, Undated; DVD-2939 (Box 14)
  - Galileo SS1 at Europa, Undated; DVD-2940 (Box 14)
  - Galileo at Callisto, Undated; DVD-2941 (Box 14)
  - Galileo SS1 at Jupiter, Undated; DVD-2942 (Box 14)
  - Comet collision!, 2005-08-03; DVD-2943 (Box 14)
  - Cassini -Huygens Mission Saturn Essays 1-3, Undated; DVD-2944 (Box 14)
  - DEEP IMPACT Launch with isolated shots, Undated; DVD-2945 (Box 14)
  - NewCONTOUR A Proposal in response to NASA AO NNH04ZSS002O, 2004-07-16; DVD-2946 (Box 27)
  - Whipple Photos, Undated; DVD-2947 (Box 14)
  - DEEP IMPACT Launch with isolated shots, Undated; DVD-2948 (Box 14)
  - DEEP IMPACT Prelaunch Press conference and Science Mission Briefing, Undated; DVD-2949 (Box 14)
  - DEEP IMPACT Launch with isolated shots, Undated; DVD-2950 (Box 14)
  - Spirit and Opportunity Mars Exploration Rover Mission, 2005-01-26; DVD-2951 (Box 14)
  - Cassini-Huygens Mission to Saturn and Titan, 2005-03; DVD-2952 (Box 14)
    Saturn Orbit Insertion, Huygens Probe Release, Entry and Decent
  - Deep Impact Encounter Pictures, Undated; DVD-2953 (Box 14)
  - E. Brooks Carl Sagan: Star Stuff, 2012; DVD-2954 (Box 14)
  - Mars Exploration Program Compilation DVD III, 2005-05-05; DVD-2955 (Box 14)
    Mars Exploration Rovers (Spirit and Opportunity), Mars Reconnaissance Orbiter
  - Deep Impact commentary, 2005-07-05; DVD-2956 (Box 14)
  - DEEP IMPACT Prelaunch Press conference and Science Mission Briefing, Undated; DVD-2957 (Box 14)
  - Ring World 2 Cassini-Huygens mission to Saturn and its moons, 2005-11; DVD-2958 (Box 14)
  - COEL Presentations Woods Hole, MA, 2011-06-07-2011-06-08; DVD-2959 (Box 14)
  - Stardust NExT, 2009-06-08; DVD-2960 (Box 14)
  - Stardust NExT, 2008-10; DVD-2961 (Box 14)
  - Inconvenient Truth "Edited", Undated; DVD-2962 (Box 14)
  - The dynamic sun version 3.0, Undated; DVD-2963 (Box 14)
    A multimedia presentaiton on the sun for windowsn and powermac users
  - SSV Science Visualization Results volume 1, 2007; DVD-2964 (Box 14)
    Science Data Delivery DVD: Kiosk Version
  - Impact! An Asteroid's Journey to Earch, 2008; DVD-2965 (Box 14)
    An Interactive DVD Program for Middle and High School
  - Spitzer Space Telescope, Undated; DVD-2966 (Box 14)
  - Mission Summary and Stereoscopic ISS Tours By Thomas Reiter, 2007; DVD-2967 (Box 14)
  - Whipple Photo, Undated; FD-927 (Box 14)
  - BELL LETTER LAS, Undated; FD-928 (Box 14)
  - Unlabeled Floppy Disk, Undated; FD-929 (Box 14)
  - OPS Movies NEAR Q-Time, 2000-10-20; ZD-91 (Box 14)
    Day 5: 263, 194
  - NEAR MSI/NIS meeting Cornell Aug 10/11, Undated; ZD-92 (Box 14)
    Presentations: Murchie #1, Murchie #2, Domingue, Prockter
  - Veverka/Cornell DPS 2000 Quicktime Movies NEAR at 433 Eros by Ms Robinson, 2000; ZD-93 (Box 14)
    000 All 3, A 263, B 193, C 201
  - CONTOUR with Music (6:30 Repeating), 2002-06; V-11163 (Box 14)
  - NEAR (Near Earch Asteroid Rendezvous) The Journey Continues - 1999 Update, 1999-03-15; V-11164 (Box 14)
  - Veverka/DPS 2000/NEAR/Eros, 2000; V-11165 (Box 14)
  - CONTOUR Animation (4:40) #19194, Undated; V-11166 (Box 14)
  - Discovery Program Unlocking the Mysteries, 2002; V-11167 (Box 14)
  - Press Release NASA CONTOUR, Spacecraft Flow, 2002-06-28; V-11168 (Box 14)
  - CONTOUR Departs Earth, 2002; V-11169 (Box 14)
  - NASA, CONTOUR spacecraft and launch vehicle flow pre-launch and launch, 2002-07-03; V-11170 (Box 14)
  - DAN MAAS www.dcine.com CONTOUR VIDEO Final Version, 2001-02-14; V-11171 (Box 14)
  - Stardust Bringing Cosmic History to Earch, V-11172 (Box 14)
  - CONTOUR Video Preliminary Final Version, Dan Maas, 2001-09-13; V-11173 (Box 14)
  - CONTOUR Departs Earch, 2002; V-11174 (Box 14)
  - CONTOUR Animation Short Edits, Undated; V-11175 (Box 14)
  - CONTOUR Animation Final Master, 2001-02-14; V-11176 (Box 14)
  - CONTOUR Stuff, Undated; V-11177 (Box 14)
  - 951 Gaspra Shape Model Rotations, 1993-05; V-11178 (Box 14)
  - NASA, CONTOUR spacecraft and launch vehicle flow pre-launch and launch, 2002-07-03; V-11179 (Box 14)
  - NEAR Shoemaker at 433 Eros 18037, 2000-09-15; V-11180 (Box 14)
  - Encke workshop Harvard University Tape #1, 2001-05-18-2001-05-19; V-11181 (Box 14)
  - Encke workshop Harvard University Tape #2, 2001-05-18-2001-05-19; V-11182 (Box 14)
  - Encke workshop Harvard University Tape #3, 2001-05-18-2001-05-19; V-11183 (Box 14)
  - NASA Presentation Veverka, 2010-09-09; HD-42 (Box 14)
  - Astronomy Powerpoints, Undated; HD-43 (Box 14)
  - Comets: Fall 1993 Edition Astromony Today, First Edition, 1993 (Box 14)
    Box of slides
  - 25 frames Ejecta Blodes Pascal Lee, 1994-07-07 (Box 14)
    Canaster of Film
  - Frames of Mars data and a greyscale test, Undated (Box 14)
- Series XI. Conferences and Talks
  - EROS talk slides (3), 1972-2001 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - 6/6/11 Woods Hole, 2011-06-06 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - 45th Meeting of the DPS, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - JPL Talk, 2011-07-18 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Washington Jan. 19 Press Conference, 2010-2011 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - 5/21/11 Denver, 2011-05-21 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - OSIRIS-REx, Undated (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Asteroids, comets, Meteors 2008, 2008-07-13-2008-07-18 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Earth and Space Sciences Division Visiting Committee External Review, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - The American Physical Society Women Speaker's List, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Proceedings of the Atacama Workshop, 2000-06-15-2000-06-17 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Phobos/Deimos: Graphics, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Comet lecture, 2008-09-10 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Comet information sheet, 2008-09-10 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Comet Halley and Giotto, informational material, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Series XII. Departmental Files
  - CWC15.1 Atronomy Photos, Undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
    (originally labeled as Photographs)
  - CWC (Connecting with cornell) Article A Look at Astronomy and Space Science at Cornell, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Chronical Article Friedlander and other articles mentioning Veverka, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - CWC (Connecting with cornell) Article A Look at Astronomy and Space Science at Cornell, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Center for Radiophysics and Space Research (CRSR), 1995-1998 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - CRSR Acting Chair and department decisions, 1995-1999 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Faculty Senate, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - CRSR 93-94, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    Removed: Published CRSR Annual Report 1993-1994
  - CRSR 95-96, 1991-1995 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    Removed: Published CRSR Annual Report 1994-1995
  - Carl Sagan's Universe, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Annual Report - JV, PG, 1996-1998 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - CRSR Annual Report 95-96, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - CRSR 1990, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - CRSR 89, 1986-1990 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    Removed: Published CRSR Annual Report 1988-1989
  - CRSR 84-85, 1984-1987 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - CRSR 83-84, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    Removed: Published CRSR Annual Report and Appendix to the Annual Report 1983-1984
  - CRSR 82-83, 1981-1983 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    Removed: Published CRSR Annual Report and Appendix to the Annual Report 1982-1983
  - CRSR 81-82, 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    Removed: Published CRSR Annual Report 1980-1981
  - New Computer Proposal, 1986-1988 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - SUN - Quick Ref. 1st, labels, Undated (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - SUN Workstation Permission, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - NSF Computer Proposal 11/94, 1994-11 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Department of Astronomy, 2001-2002 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Department of Astronomy, 2004-2005 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Faculty meeting, 2002-09 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Faculty meeting, 2003-05 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - IR Job, 2002-06-2003-03 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Palomar Project, 2002-02-2003-01 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Faculty meeting, 2002-06-19 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Faculty meeting, 2002-11-08 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Departmental review, 2003-11-2004 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Department of Astronomy, 2003-2004 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Department of Astronomy, 1999-2000 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Series XIII. Objects
  - Mars Exploration Rover Button, 2003; MU-2739 (Box 27)
  - Eros Orbit Insertion Button, 2001; MU-2740 (Box 27)
  - NEAR Eros Orbit Insertion Patch, 2000; MU-2741 (Box 27)
  - NASA - AMES Research Center LCROSS Patch, 2009; MU-2742 (Box 27)
  - Apollo 11 40th anniversery patch, 2009; MU-2743 (Box 27)
  - STARDUST NExT Pin, Undated; MU-2744 (Box 27)
  - STARDUST NExT Pin, Undated; MU-2745 (Box 27)
  - CONTOUR Pin, Undated; MU-2746 (Box 27)
  - CONTOUR Pin, Undated; MU-2747 (Box 27)
  - NEAR 253 Mathilda, 1997; MU-2748 (Box 27)
  - Original leather drive gear from Fuertes Observatory, Undated; MU-2749 (Box 27)
    Symbol of office of chairman of astronomy
  - Vial of Dust Labaled Murch G, Murchison Meteorite, Undated; MU-2750 (Box 27)
    G = 60 microns
  - Olivine Bronzite Chondrite, 157.0g, David New, 1978-12-18; MU-2763 (Box 27)
  - Contour material - accompanies MU-2762 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - CONTOUR model and stand, Undated; MU-2762
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Reports - cataloged individually in the Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections (coll number is ARP 1837)
Published CRSR Annual Report 1981-1982
Published CRSR Annual Report 1982-1983
Appendix to CRSR Annual Report, 1982-1983
Published CRSR Annual Report 1983-1984
Appendix to CRSR Annual Report, 1983-1984
Published CRSR Annual Report 1988-1989
Published CRSR Annual Report 1989-1990
Published CRSR Annual Report 1993-1994
Published CRSR Annual Report 1994-1995
Published CRSR Annual Report 1995-1996